&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：多年来，人们一直在叫嚣JavaScript，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: For years, there was clamoring that JavaScript,
如果模块作为设计模式如此重要，
if the modules were so important as a design pattern,
那么我们应该对他们有一流的语法支持。
then we ought to have first class and syntactic support for them.
因此我们最终添加了ES6模块。
And so we finally added ES6 modules.
ES6模块，&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：are，
ES6 modules, &gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Are,
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：嗯，我只想说
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Well, let me just say
他们是一个正在进行的工作。
they're a work in progress.
应该是，当ES6规范落地时，我们只有模块和
It should have been that when the ES6 spec landed, we just had modules and
然后在几个月或一年内，它只是在所有环境中。
then within a few months or a year, it was just in all environments.
不幸的是，我们遇到了一些流程故障，
Unfortunately, we had somewhat of a process breakdown,
尽我所能的慷慨，因为TC39并不是真的
to be as generous as I can, in that TC39 didn't really
与Node.js讨论他们对模块语法的计划。
talk to Node.js about their plans for the module syntax.
而Node.js并没有真正与TC39谈论什么
And Node.js didn't really talk to TC39 about the fact that what
他们即将规范与Node.js不兼容。
they were about to spec was incompatible with Node.js.
于是那个规范落地了，一年半后，终于有人
And so that spec landed, and then a year and a half later, somebody finally
意识到他们两个应该开始谈论这种不相容。
realized that the two of them should start talking about that incompatibility.
在过去的两年半时间里，我们进行了一系列的讨论
And for the last two and a half years, we've had this cluster f of discussions
而且，我们在这个存在的危机中我们要做什么
and, what are we gonna do in this existential crisis of we have this thing
这在规范中，它在浏览器中工作，但是单个最大的代码
that's in the spec and it works in browsers, but the single largest code
仓库曾经发明过，又名NPM，它是完全不兼容的吗？
repository ever invented, aka NPM, it's completely incompatible?
那我们怎么办？
So what are we gonna do?
好消息是他们一直在努力
Good news is they have been working on it,
一些非常聪明的人一直在研究它。
some really smart people have been working on it.
坏消息是只有糟糕的妥协
The bad news is there's only bad compromises
当你走到那么远的时候。
when you get that far down the road.
其中之一，我认为是非常可怕的妥协，
And one of those, what I consider to be really terrible compromises,
是要在Node中互换使用ES6模块，
is that to use ES6 modules interchangeably in Node,
你必须使用不同的文件扩展名，mjs而不是js。
you're gonna have to use a different file extension, mjs instead of js.
因此，Node内部有一个工作组正在致力于填满
So there's a working group within Node that is working on getting full
模块支持以及任何必要的警告，
module support with whatever caveats are necessary,
对Node的全面模块支持，他们将分阶段进行。
full module support into Node, and they're gonna do it over phases.
我认为，在这个时刻，他们是被期待的，
And they are expected, I think, at this moment,
预计在2020年第一季度的某个时候，它们将在Node稳定着陆
they're expected sometime in Q1 of 2020 to land stable in Node
Node中模块支持的三个或四个阶段的第一阶段。
the first phase of three or four phases of module support in Node.
这就像是规格出来五年后的事了。
That's like five years after the spec came out.
所以我们要等这么长时间也不是很好。
So that's not great that we're having to wait this long.
我实际上是这个功能的狂热粉丝，我很想写它，但是
I actually am a big fan of this feature and would like to be writing it, but
我一直袖手旁观，由于流量的原因，没有采用这种语法。
I have stayed on the sidelines and not adopted this syntax because of the flux.
有一次他们真的说他们可能不得不让TC39改变
At one point they were literally saying they may have to get TC39 to change
语法。
the syntax.
当我听到我说，我退出了。
And when I heard that I was like, I'm out.
我在等整件事平息下来，好吗？
I'm waiting for this whole thing to settle down, okay?
所以有些人是早期采用者，他们喜欢模块语法，并且
So some people were early adopters, and they loved the module syntax, and
他们整天都在写，而且他们有传送器之类的东西。
they're writing it all day, and they're having transpilers and whatever.
那很好。
And that's fine.
如果你使用这种语法，那很好。
If you use that syntax, that's great.
我会简单地向你展示一下它是什么，但是
I'm gonna show you briefly what it is, but
我只是从我的角度和你分享，
I'm just sharing with you from my perspective,
在整个Node问题解决之前，我还不会使用这种语法，对吗？
I don't use this syntax quite yet until this whole Node thing settles down, yes?
&gt；&gt；演讲者2：有没有关于什么的一两句TLDR
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Is there a one or two sentence TLDR about what
不兼容是在编写的规范之间吗？
the incompatibility is between the spec as written?
这和或有关吗？
Does it have to do with or?
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：是的，所以这不是完全的问题，但是
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Yeah, so this is not the complete problem, but
这可能是更大的问题之一。
this is probably one of the bigger problems.
节点希望保留您执行旧操作的能力
Node wants to preserve the ability for you to do an old
新样式ES6模块的样式要求，或者
style require of a new style ES6 module, or
执行旧样式Common JS模块的ES6模块样式导入。
do an ES6 module style import of an old style Common JS module.
做一个或另一个并不是很糟糕，但是
And it's not that bad to do one or the other, but
当你有一个周期的时候真的很疯狂。
it's really crazy when you have a cycle.
其中一个要求另一个，然后导入另一个，并且
Where one has required the other, and then imported the other, and
在那些角落的情况下，事情就完全变得疯狂了。
things just go completely nuts in those corner cases.
因为他们拥有如此庞大而充满活力的生态系统，
And because they have such a large and vibrant ecosystem,
他们不得不担心那些角落里的案子。
they have to worry about all those corner cases.
所以有一大堆问题，他们一直在筛选，做出妥协。
So there's a bunch of problems, they've been sifting them out, making compromises.
我不喜欢结果
I don't like the outcome,
但我很高兴我们至少在取得进展方面取得了进展。
but I'm glad that we're at least making progress towards getting something.
这不会很令人惊讶，但至少它是有意义的，好吗？
It's not gonna be amazing, but at least it's something, okay?
当它着陆时，我完全打算切换到语法。
And when it lands, I fully intend to switch over to the syntax.
但现在，如果我真的需要支持的话，这是其中一件事，
But for now, this is one of those things that if I really needed to support it,
我更喜欢一个工具来为我编写语法，以便工具可以更改和
I would prefer a tool to write me the syntax so that a tool can change and
处理这些问题。
deal with those problems.
这不是我的创作格式。
This is not an authoring format for me.
我继续使用成语，古典风格。
I continue to use the idiom, the classic style.
下面是模块格式的样子。
So here's what the module format looks like.
你打开一个文件，你就开始制作变量和函数。
You open up a file and you just start making variables and functions.
还有那个文件，因为它将被加载为一个模块，
And that file, because it's gonna be loaded as a module,
假设一切都是私人的。
is assumed that everything is private.
您不需要语法包装器。
You don't need a syntactic wrapper.
您可以在概念上认为它被包装在一个大函数中。
You can conceptually of think of it is being wrapped in a big function.
包装在默认情况下为私有的作用域中。
Wrapped in a scope that is by default private.
公开的方式是使用export关键字，
The way you make something public is you use the export keyword,
就像你在3号线上看到的。
like you see on line 3.
所以你出口的任何东西都是公开的，
So anything you export is public,
所有你不出口的东西都是私人的。
everything that you don't export is private.
关于模块需要了解的另一件事是，它们是基于文件的。
The other thing to know about modules is that they are file-based.
这意味着同一文件中不可能有多个ES6模块。
Which means it is impossible to have more than one ES6 module in the same file.
如果您的应用程序由1000个模块组成，
If your application is composed of say, 1,000 modules,
您的许多应用程序都是这样的，并且您在ES6模块中编写了所有这些应用程序，
the way many of your applications are, and you write all of them in ES6 modules,
您将把它们都作为单独的文件编写，这是很好的。
you'll be writing them all as separate files, which is fine.
但你不会有办法拿到那些ES6
But there will not be a way for you to take those ES6
模块的当前形式，并将它们放入相同的文件中。
modules in their current form and ever put them into the same file.
这不是一件事。
That's not a thing.
例如，在没有构建过程的情况下，
So for example, without a build process,
如果你想把它们送到浏览器上，你就得加载一千个
if you wanted to ship them to a browser, you're gonna have to load a thousand
单独的文件及其所有性能影响。
separate files with all the performance implications thereof.
现在正在做这件事的人们正在使用他们创作的工具
People that are currently doing this today are using tools where they author
在ES6模块中，他们编译回老式的模块和
in ES6 modules and they compile back to the old school style module and
将它们连接到一个文件中，然后将其发送出去。
concatenate them into a file and ship it off.
在我看来，我只是跳过了中间人。
And in my opinion, I'm just skipping the middleman.
因为无论如何我们都必须编译回旧语法，
Since we have to compile back to that old syntax anyway,
我只是一直在写旧的语法。
I just keep writing that old syntax.
但是有些人发现创作这种格式的好处。
But some people are finding benefit out of authoring this format.
所以你制作一个模块，然后输出你想要的东西。
So you make a module and you export what you want.
需要知道的另一件事是，它们不仅是基于文件的，而且它们也是单例。
The other thing to know, not only are they file-based, but they're also singletons.
无论您将此模块导入应用程序多少次，
No matter how many times you import this module into an application,
它只运行一次。
it only ever runs once.
每隔一次你导入它，
And every other time that you import it,
您只需获得对同一实例的另一个引用。
you just get another reference to that same instance.
因此，如果你想为你的模块建立一个工厂，人们可以在那里制造多个
So if you want to have a factory for your modules where people can make multiple
实例，您必须在API上公开一个工厂函数来实现这一点。
instances, you're gonna have to expose on your API, a factory function to do that.